motorpoint.co.uk 2019-09-10

# Motorpoint Privacy Policy | Motorpoint

This privacy policy sets out how Motorpoint Limited collects, uses and protects any information that you give us when you use our services and this website. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.

## What information do we collect about you?

We collect information about you in the following ways:

  * Information that you provide to us - by filling out forms on our site [Motorpoint.co.uk](https://www.motorpoint.co.uk/) or by corresponding with us by phone, email or in person. This includes information you provide when you subscribe to MyMotorpoint, when you subscribe to our marketing communications, enter a promotion or competition, use live chat, make an email enquiry, reserve a vehicle or complete a customer care contact form.
  * Website information that is collected using cookies.
  * When it is passed to us from third party referrers, such as Autotrader.

## What we do with the information we gather

We use the information we hold about you in the following ways:

  * To process your order and carry out obligations under your purchase agreement and to provide you with information, products and services that you request from us.
  * If you have consented, to periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * If you have consented, occasionally to send an email to carry out market research.
  * We do not pass any of your information to a 3rd party for marketing.
  * If you require finance for a purchase, we will need to share some of your details with the lender (further details can be found at our [finance pages](https://www.motorpoint.co.uk/finance)) and if you buy products such as MAP, warranty or paint protection, we will need to share some of your details with the policy administrator, Autoprotect.
  * To comply with our legal obligations with the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) (in ensuring we treat our customers fairly and can then evidence this to the FCA).

## Marketing – your rights

We would like to send you information about our products and services which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receiving marketing, you may opt out at a later date.

If you have a MyMotorpoint account, you can manage your preferences online by logging in and browsing to communication preferences.

You have the right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted, please click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our communications.

## Access to your information

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like some or all of your personal information sent to you, please fill in a [copy of our form](https://mpcdn.azureedge.net/documents/dsar-form.pdf) and email us at [dpo@motorpoint.co.uk](mailto:dpo@motorpoint.co.uk?subject=Access%20request) or write to us at:

Customer Care Team  
Motorpoint Derby  
Chartwell Drive  
Derby, DE21 6BZ

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website as some features may not function as a result.

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and any changes to it will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. This policy was last updated on 23 April 2018.

## Our contact

We welcome any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you, which should be sent to us:

  * By email at [customercare@motorpoint.co.uk](mailto:%20customercare@motorpoint.co.uk?subject=Privacy%20policy%20question)
  * By post to Customer Care Team, Motorpoint Derby, Chartwell Drive, Derby, DE21 6BZ
